Hi, I'm Les Whitley.
I'd like to talk to you right now about how to slim the waist.
The waist or the mid section, abdominals, or commonly called the core, can be slimmed in several different ways.
Most importantly by minimizing the amount of body fat that's covering the musculature of the structure itself.
Toning the muscles and keeping the muscles tight will help pull them in, so they act like a natural girdle for the body.
Reducing the amount of body fat overlying that tissue would help again, slim that area, to give it overall appearance of a leaner, stronger mid section.
By strengthening and toning the rest of the muscles of your body will give you a nice overall V-shape look, which gives you nice strong shoulders and upper body, a good balanced lower body for strength and development there, but then maximizing that narrow waist by modifying your diet, so that it's overall adding to your health, as well as increasing your level of activity to achieve maximum results.
Spend time doing abdominal exercises that target all aspects, moving the core and training the core as one.
After all it's the connection between your upper body and your lower body.
And it's not necessarily one specific isolation exercise that's going to provide everything that you need.
Do a variety of different exercises, as your abdominal and mid section, as well as your core, is used in almost everything that you do, it gets trained frequently throughout the day.
So take time, focus, add that healthy diet, as well as regular exercise to your routine, to achieve that nice slim waist.